A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1972-1986
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 32673], 1984, Extent: 10 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 1-10)
  - Mines and Quarries, Division of, 1984 (Box 10)
  - VOSH, OSHA, and Right to Work, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Marine Products Commission, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Artificial Reef Program, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Crabbing regulations, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Marine Resources Commission, 1984 (Box 10)
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 37780], 1972-1980, Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1980 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1980 (Box 2)
  - Administrative-Janice's box, 1972-1980 (Box 3)
  - Cheatham Annex, 1972-1980 (Box 4)
  - Cheatham Annex, 1972-1980 (Box 5)
  - Studies and reports, 1972-1980 (Box 6)
  - Studies and reports, 1972-1980 (Box 7)
  - Budget, 1972-1980 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1972-1980 (Box 9)
  - Printed materials and reports, 1972-1980 (Box 10)
  - Printed materials and reports, 1972-1980 (Box 11)